maritimworld.com 2012-06-06

# Maritimworld - Privacy Policy

Please enter your email address to subscribe  
for weekly newsletter.

**Privacy**

This website is designed to allow individuals to shop online at Maritim World. Maritim World recognizes that it is critical for individuals to be confident that their privacy is protected when they visit our website, MaritimWorld. Privacy procedures regarding information collected from users of this website are consistent with the provisions of the Internet Security and Privacy Act. Below, what information is collected and how that information is used is described. This privacy policy only applies to this website. MaritimWorld. does not collect any personal information about you unless you provide that information voluntarily.

**Information Collected**

When you E-mail us or Complete a Transaction during your visit to this website you may send MaritimWorld your e-mail address and the contents of your message will be collected. The information collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video, and graphic information formats included in the message. Your e-mail address and the information included in your message will be used to respond to you, to address issues you identify, to improve this website, or to forward you information as it relates to MaritimWorld. MaritimWorld.  will not sell or otherwise disclose your e-mail address for any other purpose. You may also opt to complete a transaction/purchase while visiting our site. The information, including personal information, credit card information, etc. volunteered by you in completing the transaction is used by MaritimWorld is only to process your transaction.

**Disclosure of Information Collected Through This Website**

The collection of information through this website and the disclosure of that information are subject to the provisions of the Internet Security and Privacy Act. MaritimWorld. will only collect personal information through this website or disclose personal information collected through this website if the user has consented to the collection or disclosure of such personal information. The voluntary disclosure of personal information to MaritimWorld by the user, whether solicited or unsolicited, constitutes consent.  
  
---
